I have had to change wear parts here on the plow.
New cuts and lace.
You may not see that, but it is a little green on the inserts.
It is worn now.
It does not cut down with the old spests and inserts, so I had to change them.
It plows pretty well now.
Although you see that it is dry.
Today I sit in the MXU and plow and not in the MX.
The MX had been more beautiful, because it has a working AC.
One may take what is free
Then you do not have to do this loader,
On the MX as well.
Because it is always in the way.
Here it will be wheat as I said.
I have plowed two more pieces as it will be wheat.
That's the only thing we're going to be autumn this year.
The three pieces.
The four pieces we had with wheat and rye wheat, it will be spring grains with sowing next year
There will be Vall in two years on them.
It does not go very fast and
Plow.
You lie and
Sneak in three km/h.
I do not know how fun you have to sit and glare at me when I drive here and talk noise ...
I may not have that much quality right now.
Don't have so many new machines to show you.
I have gone through the tractors, with buttons and that.
I have gone through the plow twice.
So that...
This tractor I have nothing more to say about really.
Clutch -free front and back.
Have all the modern tractors, or the murders hardly have it anymore.
This one has ordinary brakes and no abdominal brakes, or lamella connection.
This is the loader lever.
The lamp that shines means that the implement lock is unlocked.
So that I can put on a scoop.
You could say it's like an aircraft lever.
If you pull it against you, you raise the loader and press it forward and lower the loader.
If you pull it against you, it tilts up.
If you push away the lever, you ted up the loader bracket.
It's like an aircraft lever about.
Looks pretty good, the plowing here.
There it stretched up stone the trigger.
Drove on a stone there.
It was not as nicely plowed right there.
I don't learn to finish this bit today.
The time is
16:31 here.
Do not intend to drive so long tonight.
It is not so wide, but it is long.
There are pieces that we usually around this everything in principle.
Right here is not ours.
It is probably the only one in this particular thing here.
Yes, I don't know if I should say so much more.
I bring the camera today when I plow I thought,
So that it becomes a movie.
So that you do not lose interest completely
May we see what I do next time.
If you have any ideas, you are welcome to leave a comment.
It can be difficult to solve certain things.
If you may want to see specific machines, which I do not have.